Conversation starters is a great tool for getting deeper and more interesting information
when you're out in the field.
This can be especially helpful when you're dealing with cultures other than your own.
As an example, when we were recently doing a project in Mexico to design savings programs,
we actually started with some concepts to get people to react and start to talk to us
in ways that they might not otherwise if we had just asked simple questions.
So what you see here are examples of a couple different things we created.
Around the question of how people might want to access their money.
We put money in a brick, we put money in a pillow, we put money in an envelope.
None of these are actually the concepts we intend to design, but what they do is create
a great way for people to react and give us more information around how they feel or
how they think about something rather than just simply asking a basic question.